Susan Lee

Clinical Research Coordinator II

sohzahn@gmail.com

Division of Allergy and Immunology Children's Hospital of Philadelphia

Clinical research coordinator with 4 years of experience in study start-up, close-out, collaboration with external sites, regulatory submissions, and database creation, cleanup, and management. Looking to apply the skills I am learning from a full-stack coding bootcamp to get into web development or data visualization.

Education

Drexel University, Philadelphia, PA B.S. in Health Sciences

Dec 2017

Research Experience

Clinical Research Coordinator II

Aug 2021 – Present

Children's Hospital of Philadelphia, Division of Allergy and Immunology, Philadelphia, PA

PI: Jonathan Spergel, MD, PhD

- Assisted in conduct of multiple biologic clinical trials from Phase I to III. Includes NIH-funded, industry-sponsored, and investigator-initiated studies in Allergy/Immunology (i.e., eosinophilic esophagitis (EoE) and eosinophilic gastritis)
- Submitted regulatory documents independently and assisted coworkers and other PIs with submissions
- Facilitated in-person and remote monitoring visits, investigational drug monitoring visits, and study close-out visits
- Independently lead coworkers' study visits and procedures
- Assisted with onboarding and mentoring multiple new coworkers simultaneously (RAs, CRCs, and nurse CRCs)

Clinical Research Coordinator

July 2020 - July 2021

University of Pennsylvania, Department of Cardiology, Philadelphia, PA PI: Han Yuchi, MD, MMSc

- Assisted in conduct of cardiac MRI research studies, including an NIH-funded, investigator-initiated observational study
- Developed SOPs, case report forms, and online databases (REDCap) for study visits and site initiation
- Scheduled and conducted initial and follow-up visits, labs, and procedures with patients
- Created a REDCap project to serve as the study's data management and coordinating center (DMCC)
- Processed and stored blood biospecimens for future biobanking
- Collaborated with external sites for local study protocol implementation

Clinical Research Assistant

Nov 2018 – July 2020

University of Pennsylvania, Basser Center for BRCA, Philadelphia, PA

PI: Susan Domchek, MD

- Entered patient medical and family history into an oncology genetics registry database
- Abstracted data from medical charts, outside medical records, and pathology reports
- Assisted with database queries to resolve data discrepancies for multiple research protocols
- Performed ad-hoc queries for data cleanup

Certifications & Software

iMedidata (RAVE), REDCap, CITI GCP Training, BLS CPR, EPIC, Penn CTMS, OnCore, ERT

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, MySQL, Node.js, APIs, React.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Python